W
Wh
Wha
What
What i
What if
What if b
What if bu
What if bui
What if buil
What if build
What if buildi
What if buildin
What if building
What if building a
What if building a g
What if building a gl
What if building a glo
What if building a glob
What if building a globa
What if building a global
c
co
What if building a global
com
comm
What if building a global
commu
commun
What if building a global
communi
communit
What if building a global
community
community w
What if building a global
community wa
community was
What if building a global
community was e
community was ea
What if building a global
community was eas
community was easy
What if building a global
community was easy.
community was easy..
What if building a global
community was easy...
community was easy...?